{
    "subject": "resource/Boris_Kalin",
    "predicate": "ontology/training",
    "object": "resource/Zagreb",
    "human_readable": "Boris Kalin was trained in Zagreb.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9782785177230835,
            "question": "What kind of training did Boris Kalin undertake in Zagreb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8412123918533325,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Boris Kalin's time in Zagreb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7945971488952637,
            "question": "What city was involved in Boris Kalin's training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772214949131012,
            "question": "Where did Boris Kalin receive his training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369174718856812,
            "question": "In which location was Boris Kalin educated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521080493927002,
            "question": "Where did Boris Kalin's studies take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47934678196907043,
            "question": "How was Boris Kalin's education structured?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4770055413246155,
            "question": "What city played a role in Boris Kalin's development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.396330863237381,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Boris Kalin's educational background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39248520135879517,
            "question": "What is known about Boris Kalin's education history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Boris Kalin was trained in Zagreb.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7024_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Boris Kalin's educational background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7024_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city played a role in Boris Kalin's development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7024_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was Boris Kalin's education structured?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7024_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7024_49.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that in one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7024/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt), it is mentioned that Boris Kalin attended the technical secondary school in Ljubljana and continued his studies between 1924 and 1929 at the Zagreb Academy of Fine Arts with the professors Rudolf Valdec, Frano Kr\u0161ini\u0107, Ivo Kredi\u0107 and Ivan Me\u0161trovi\u0107. This information directly supports the triple statement that Boris Kalin was trained in Zagreb."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Kalin attended the technical secondary school in Ljubljana and continued his studies between 1924 and 1929 at the Zagreb Academy of Fine Arts with the professors Rudolf Valdec, Frano Kr\u0161ini\u0107, Ivo Kredi\u0107 and Ivan Me\u0161trovi\u0107.\" This confirms that Boris Kalin was indeed trained in Zagreb."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}